simplify360.com 2019-04-10

# Simplify360 | Privacy Policy

Effective date: May 23, 2018

Simplify360 ("us", "we", or "our") operates the http://www.simplify360.com website (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from http://www.simplify360.com

#### Definitions

  * **Service**

Service is the http://www.simplify360.com website operated by Simplify360

  * **Personal Data**

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

  * **Usage Data**

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

  * **Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer or mobile device).

  * **Data Controller**

Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.

  * **Data Processors (or Service Providers)**

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

  * **Data Subject (or User)**

Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data.

#### Information Collection And Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

#### Types of Data Collected

#### Simplify360 Services & Personal Data

Simplify360 is a SAAS based social media management platform. Simplify360 allows its users to integrate their social networks together in Simplify360 platform and may also allow integrating CRM (Customer relationship Management) applications used by an organization. The social media contents processed by Simplify360 are user-generated, public and as per the guidelines of social media networks. Such contents might contain personal data shared by end users in the Social Media. Since such data are processed by Simplify360 and used by its customers, GDPR apply for both Simplify360 and its customers in different ways. 

Simplify360 also allows its customers to provide customer support to the end customers. During the course of customer support activity, Simplify360 customer may collect the end user's personal details like email id, phone number, first name, last name and the account id of the end customer and store it in Simplify360 platform. Such personal informations are voluntarily shared by end customers for the purpose of customer support. Simplify360 is an enterprise CRM platform and doesn't collect end user data directly in any manner. 

As with the law it replaces, the GDPR distinguishes between organisations that are “data controllers” and those that are “data processors”. As explained in our Privacy Policy, Simplify360 is a data processor of content generated, requested or published via its supported platforms in accordance with the instructions our customers give us through our services. Because our customers control how their content is collected and used by them, our customers are, in legal terms, the data controllers of the content that they process through our platform. Simplify360 is its customers’ data processor of that content. 

Simplify360 is a secure platform and user needs to login using user name and the passwords. While providing the access to our platform customers we may ask user to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Email address
  * First name and last name
  * Phone number
  * Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with transactional alerts, newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.

#### Usage Data

We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

#### Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

  * **Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
  * **Preference Cookies.** We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  * **Security Cookies.** We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

#### Use of Data

Simplify360 uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain our Service
  * To notify you about changes to our Service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer support
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
  * To monitor the usage of our Service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

#### Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), Simplify360 legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

Simplify360 may process your Personal Data because:

  * We need to perform a contract with you
  * You have given us permission to do so
  * The processing is in our legitimate interests and it's not overridden by your rights
  * For payment processing purposes
  * To comply with the law

#### Retention of Data

Simplify360 will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

Simplify360 will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

#### Transfer Of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Simplify360 will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

#### Disclosure Of Data

#### Disclosure for Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, Simplify360 may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

#### Legal Requirements

Simplify360 may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Simplify360
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

#### Security Of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Simplify360 aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

  * **The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.** Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.

  * **The right of rectification.** You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.

  * **The right to object.** You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.

  * **The right of restriction.** You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.

  * **The right to data portability.** You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.

  * **The right to withdraw consent.** You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Simplify360 relied on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

#### Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

#### Payments

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

Simplify360 Shall invoice and Customer shall pay the fees as per the billing & payment terms defined on the MSA. All taxes and other governmental charges are addition to the fees charged. All payment obligations are non-cancelable and all amounts paid are non-refundable except as otherwise expressly stated in this MSA or the applicable Order forms. 

The payment processors we work with are:

  * **PayPal**

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>

  * **CCavenue**

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at []()

#### Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

#### Children's Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers. 

#### Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

  * By email: contact@simplify360.com
  * By visiting this page on our website: www.simplify360.com/
